택시 창밖으로 번지는 불빛
Lights blurring outside the taxi window.
라디오에서 흘러나온 옛날 노래
An old song playing on the radio.
이 시간엔 모든 게 느려져
Everything slows down at this hour.
너한테 갈까 말까 고민만 해
I just keep wondering whether to go to you or not.
편의점 앞 벤치에 앉아서
Sitting on a bench in front of the convenience store,
따뜻한 캔 하나 손에 쥐고
Holding a warm can in my hand.
네 연락을 기다리는 건 아닌데
It's not like I'm waiting for your call,
자꾸 화면을 확인하게 돼
But I keep checking my screen.
새벽 두 시 주파수가 맞는 밤
A 2 AM night when the frequency matches,
잡음 사이로 네 목소리가 들려
I can hear your voice through the static.
이 도시가 잠들면 우리만 깨어서
When this city falls asleep, only we stay awake,
같은 하늘 아래 다른 곳에서
In different places under the same sky.
옥상에서 내려다본 골목길
The alleyway seen from the rooftop,
가로등 하나가 깜빡이고 있어
A streetlamp is flickering.
하고 싶은 말은 루프처럼 돌아
The words I want to say go around in a loop,
입 밖으론 한마디도 못 꺼내
But I can't utter a single word.
이어폰 한쪽만 끼고 걸어
I walk with only one earphone in,
네가 좋아하던 그 노래 틀어
Playing that song you used to like.
발걸음이 리듬을 타는 밤
A night where my footsteps follow the rhythm,
혼자인데 혼자가 아닌 것 같아
I'm alone, but it doesn't feel like I am.
새벽 두 시 주파수가 맞는 밤
A 2 AM night when the frequency matches,
잡음 사이로 네 목소리가 들려
I can hear your voice through the static.
이 도시가 잠들면 우리만 깨어서
When this city falls asleep, only we stay awake,
같은 하늘 아래 다른 곳에서
In different places under the same sky.
전화할까 말까 세 번째 고민
Wondering for the third time if I should call,
나도 지금 네 번호 보고 있어
I'm also looking at your number right now.
새벽 두 시 주파수가 맞는 밤
A 2 AM night when the frequency matches,
잡음 속에서 결국 너를 찾아
In the static, I finally find you.
이 도시가 잠들어도 우리는 깨어서
Even if this city sleeps, we stay awake,
같은 주파수로 이어져 있어
We're connected by the same frequency.